http://www.neurotechnology.com/privacy.html

Biometrics for Integrators
Large-scale multi-biometricsMegaMatcher SDKMegaMatcher AcceleratorMegaMatcher On Card SDK
Single biometricsVeriFinger SDKFingerCell SDKFree Fingerprint Verification SDKVeriLook SDKFace Verification SDKVeriEye SDKVeriSpeak SDK
Menu
Large-scale Biometric SolutionsProduct AdvisorBiometrics On-premiseMegaMatcher ABISBiometrics on CloudMegaMatcher ABIS Cloud Service
Biometric for IntegratorsProduct AdvisorProduct SchemaLarge-scale systemsMegaMatcher SDKMegaMatcher AcceleratorMegaMatcher On Card SDKFingerprint SDKVeriFinger SDKFingerCell SDKFree Fingerprint Verification SDKFace SDKVeriLook SDKFace Verification SDKFace Recognition API on Cloudat Sky Biometry websiteSentiVeillance SDKSentiMask SDKIris SDKVeriEye SDKVoice SDKVeriSpeak SDKCustom projects
Biometrics for End UsersVideo SurveillanceSentiVeillance Server Solution for VMSAttendance ManagementNCheck Bio Attendance Cloud or on-premise systems availableFace hiding in videosNVeiler Video Filter plug-in for VirtualDubGestural/voice controlNPointer Freeware app for WindowsAge Estimation by FaceCheck My Age Free Android app
Biometric ScannersSupported devicesFingerprint readers (166)Face cameras / webcamsIris scanners (18)ShopBuy scannersat Biometric Supply website
Video SurveillanceReady-to-use for VMSSentiVeillance ServerFor IntegratorsSentiVeillance SDK
Computer VisionImage Recognition PlatformSentiSight Cloud Service3D face trackingSentiMask SDKGaze trackingSentiGaze SDK3D reconstructionSentiSculpt SDK
AI-based Stock RankingStockGeist.ai
EngineeringRobotics & A.I.SentiBotics KitSentiBotics Navigation SDKBrain-computer interfaceBrainAccess development kitUltrasound technologiesUltrasound Research GroupDirectional speakerFocusonics
Privacy Policy
Collecting Personal Information
When you access our web site, our web server software records this information:
the device type you are using for accessing our website (PC, mobile phone or tablet);
your operating system type and version;
your browser type and version.
When you are placing an order via our website, we will request you for a certain information:
Your name;
Your physical address;
Phone number and email address.
Cookie usage
We use cookies – special text files, which are stored on your computer or device by your web browser when you access our website.
The cookie usage can be altered or completely disabled in browser's settings, but in this case some services on our website will be no longer available.
These types of cookies are used:
Session cookies: we store an anonymous session identifier for ensuring appropriate user experience while placing online orders or using customer-related services.
Statistics cookies: we collect anonymous browsing statistics through our partner Google Analytics.
Using and Managing Personal Information
Neurotechnology uses the information mentioned above only for processing the orders, which are placed on our website, as well as providing customer support.
Neurotechnology will not share your personal information to any company or person outside our company.
We are making our best efforts to protect users' personal information while they are using our website.
You can contact our Data Protection Officer directly if you have any questions.
Representatives
Argentina & Venezuela,
China,
India,
Sri Lanka,
USA.
Distributors
Argentina,
Brazil,
Chile,
China,
Colombia,
Congo D.R.,
El Salvador,
Greece,
India,
Israel,
Italy,
Korea,
Nigeria,
Paraguay,
Peru,
Singapore,
South Africa,
Spain,
UK,
USA,
Venezuela.
Follow us
Copyright © 1998 - 2020 Neurotechnology | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Career
